<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "../../dtd/technicalContent/dtd/task.dtd">

<task id = "Chapter2.0" xml:lang="en-us">
	<title>Table Settings - General Configuration Properties</title>
		<shortdesc>This section is for users to insert information about the data file that is to be loaded. Most of these files will come as CSV (Comma Separated Values) or PSV (Pipe Separated Values) files, both of which consist of rows and columns like an Excel file. Information about the data file and then its columns need to be recorded and below is the method for inserting the initial information about the data file itself.
		</shortdesc>
		<taskbody>
			<steps>
				<step><cmd>Source File Name</cmd>
					<info>Insert the Source File Name in full to this field. Also remember to include the extension type of the file, into this field.
					</info>
				</step>
				
				<step><cmd>Descriptor File Name</cmd>
					<info>The Descriptor File Name is for the user to enter the name of the data file in this field, but without numbers or its extension. The value in this field will become the name of the XML file created. </info>
				</step>

				<step><cmd>Description</cmd>
					<info>In this field, the user is expected to fill up a short description of the file that is being loaded.</info>
				</step>

				<step><cmd>Destination Table</cmd>
					<info>All data files are eventually loaded into Kollect Database and in this Destination Table field, the user needs to specify the database table where the data will be loaded to.</info>
				</step>

				<step><cmd>Table Sequence Name</cmd>
					<info>The table sequence name specifies the sequence used to generate Primary Keys. Here, the user is supposed to enter the Database Table Name, followed by _ID.</info>
				</step>

				<step><cmd>Generated Key</cmd>
					<info>The Generated Key specifies the name of the Primary Key column. In Kollect’s Database Tables, the Primary Key Column is always the ID column and as such, this field’s value is always, ID</info>
				</step>

				<step><cmd>Column Delimiter</cmd>
					<info>The Column Delimiter dropdown is to specify how the data is separated in the Data File, and it would be either Comma ( , ) or Pipe ( | ) so the user is required to select how the data is separated.</info>
				</step>

				<step><cmd>Date Format</cmd>
					<info>The Date Format here is to specify how dates are formatted in the data file received from the tenant. Date Format Options are selectable by the drop down menu, however the most commonly used date format is ddMMyyyy.</info>
				</step>

				<step><cmd>Include Load Execution</cmd>
					<info>The user is required to switch this button ON</info>
				</step>


			</steps>
		</taskbody>
</task>